A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, AIA-IBEC, Series B FA339
Rockefeller Archive Center
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Grady Caddo Counties, Oklahoma - North Cement Area, 1954-1956 (Box 18, Folder 190)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Hardin County, Texas - Batson Area, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 191)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Hardin County, Texas, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 192)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Hardin County, Texas - Batson Area Gulf - Choate Fee #1, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 193)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Hardin County, Texas - Batson Area Gulf - Choate Fee #2, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 194)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Hardin County, Texas - Batson Area Gulf - Choate Fee #3, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 195)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Hardin County, Texas - Batson Area Gulf - Choate Fee #4, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 196)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Hardin County, Texas - Batson Area Gulf - Choate Fee #5, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 197)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Hardin County, Texas - Batson Area Gulf - Choate Fee #6, 1955-1956 (Box 19, Folder 198)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Hardin County, Texas - Batson Area Gulf - Choate Fee #7, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 199)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Hardin County, Texas - Batson Area Gulf - Choate Fee #8, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 200)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Hardin County, Texas - Batson Area Gulf - Choate Fee #10, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 201)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Hardin County, Texas - Batson Area - Choate #1-3, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 202)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Hardin County, Texas - Batson Area - Choate #1-4, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 203)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Hardin County, Texas - Batson Area - Choate #1-5, 1955-1956 (Box 19, Folder 204)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Hardin County, Texas - Batson Area - Choate #1-6, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 205)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Hardin County, Texas - Batson Area - Choate #1-7, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 206)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Hardin County, Texas - Batson Area - Choate #1-8, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 207)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Hardin County, Texas - Batson Area - Choate #2-6, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 208)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - La Fourche Parish, Louisiana - La Fourche Prospect, 1954-1956 (Box 20, Folder 209)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Lea County, New Mexico - #1 Lea State "De", 1954 (Box 20, Folder 210)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Legal, Lea County, New Mexico - #1 Lea State "De", 1954 (Box 20, Folder 211)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Morgan County, Colorado - Loose #1, 1954-1955 (Box 20, Folder 212)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Refugio County, Texas - Welder Ranch Area, 1954-1955 (Box 20, Folder 213)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Refugio County, Texas - Welder Ranch Area, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 214)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Seminole County, Oklahoma, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 215)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Starr Zappata Counties, Texas - El Javali Prospect, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 216)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Victoria County, Texas - North Cologne Area, 1954-1956 (Box 20, Folder 217)
- IBEC - Oil Investment - Crebbs' - Yoakum County, Texas, 1954-1955 (Box 20, Folder 218)
- IBEC - General Correspondence, 1958-1971 (Box 21, Folder 219)
  Correspondence, memos re: meetings, appointments, etc.; press releases; some printed material.
- IBEC - General, 1947-1971 (Box 21, Folder 220)
  Requests for information; proposals for IBEC; correspondence re: IBEC related industries and projects; letters offering opportunities to invest in South America.
- IBEC - General - IBEC VBEC (Venezuelan Basic Economy Corporation) Memoranda, 1949 (Box 21, Folder 221)
- IBEC - General - "Requests for Information", 1949-1959 (Box 21, Folder 222)
  Requests for information and replies sent.
- IBEC - Annual Operations Workshop Meetings, 1967-1969 (Box 21, Folder 223)
  Letters, memos; rough notes - open fall meeting talk, 1967.
- IBEC - Advisory Board Meeting - Zurich, May 16, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 224)
  Memo re: program, attendance of meeting.
- IBEC - Board of Directors - Correspondence Memos, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 225)
  Correspondence re: election of directors.
- IBEC - Board of Directors - Meetings, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 226)
  Memos re: meetings of Board of Directors, June-November 1971; minutes of meetings; text of agreement between IBEC Housing Co. (IHC) of Oklahoma and Aztec Development Co.
- IBEC - Regular Meeting of Board of Directors of IBEC, March 23, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 227)
- IBEC - Budgets, 1971-1972 (Box 22, Folder 228)
  Consolidated budgets 1971, 1971; memos re: 1971 budget.
- IBEC - Chase Manhattan Bank, 1959, 1960, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 229)
  Correspondence and memos re: Chase Manhattan Bank Trust Loan Agreement.
- IBEC - Corporate Development Plan III, 1969-1971 (Box 22, Folder 230)
- IBEC - Africa, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 231)
  Memos re: interests in Belgian Congo, Rhodesia and Nyasaland and Nigeria.
- IBEC - Brazil, 1957-1958 (Box 22, Folder 232)
  Memos re: IBEC interests in Brazil.
- IBEC - Directory for IBEC and Affiliated Co.'s, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 233)
- IBEC - Letters of Appreciation on NAR's Return to Office, March 1956 (Box 22, Folder 234)
- IBEC - History of IBEC Luncheon, December 1967 - April 1968 (Box 22, Folder 235)
  Correspondence and memos re: Wayne Broehl's book "The International Basic Economy Corporation;" press releases and fact sheet on IBEC; addresses of NAR and Ambassador Linowitz at luncheon April 11, 1968; memos re: luncheon; reprint of "The MBA - Venture in Venezuela" by Wayne Broehl.
- IBEC - Housing Corporation - General and Applications, 1954-1966 (Box 22, Folder 236)
  Requests for special consideration in re: to housing projects; requests for information on housing; individuals making applications for jobs.
- IBENCO - T. C. Streibert, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 237)
  Memos on Tenco and IBEC; requests for information; applications for positions with IBENCO; correspondence on marketing coffee.
- IBEC - Meetings, March 3, 1947 - May 21, 1948 (Box 22, Folder 238)
  10:30 meeting minutes.
- IBEC - Meetings, June 4, 1948 - January 12, 1949 (Box 22, Folder 239)
- IBEC - Meetings, January 14, 1949 - December 21, 1949 (Box 22, Folder 240)
- IBEC - Meetings, March 15, 1950 - October 9, 1951 (Box 22, Folder 241)
- IBEC - Meetings, October 9, 1951 - May 4, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 242)
- IBEC - Public Affairs Report, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 243)
- IBEC - McKinsey and Co. Study, March 1952 (Box 23, Folder 244)
- Preliminary Economic and Industrial Report on the United States of Venezuela, 1940 (Box 23, Folder 245)
  Copy 1.
- Preliminary Economic and Industrial Report on the United States of Venezuela, 1940 (Box 23, Folder 246)
  Copy 2.
- International Basic Economy Corporation, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 247)
- IBEC - Report - Reviews, 1965-1971 (Box 23, Folder 248)
  Press releases re: reports; reports to shareholders; memos; management review February 22, 1966.
- IBEC - Aldrich, Richard S., 1957-1966 (Box 24, Folder 249)
  Miscellaneous correspondence re: IBEC in Brazil.
- IBEC - Allyn, Kay Management Services, Venezuela, 1968-1971 (Box 24, Folder 250)
  Correspondence re: miscellaneous clippings to NAR.
- IBEC - Camp, John R., 1957-1970 (Box 24, Folder 251)
  Report on trip to Liberia, Ghana, and Nigeria, June, 1957; correspondence re: AIA and IBEC operations in Latin America; reports on programs and projects.
- IBEC - Coles, William T., 1948-1965 (Box 24, Folder 252)
  Miscellaneous re: VBEC (Venezuelan Basic Economy Corporation); reports on projects; memos on meetings; correspondence re: management; Coles elected director, 1954; above's sale of IBEC stock, 1965.
- IBEC - Crawford, Walter L., 1960-1968 (Box 24, Folder 253)
  Miscellaneous correspondence re: AIA in Brazil, several projects meetings, retirement, 1968.
- IBEC - Friele, Berent, 1949-1960 (Box 24, Folder 254)
  Memos re: IBEC in Latin America; correspondence re: business in Brazil.
- IBEC - Lockwood, John E., 1947-1951 (Box 24, Folder 255)
  Chairman of Executive Committee, 1949. Correspondence re: IBEC in Brazil and Venezuela; reports on projects and investment.
- IBEC - Meads, Donald E. - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 256)
  Reports on projects, investments, executive committee meetings; trip notes, Brussels meeting, INSA, finances, operating statistics.
- IBEC - Meads, Donald E. - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 257)
- IBEC - Meads, Donald E. - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 258)
- IBEC - Meads, Donald E. - Correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 25, Folder 259)
- IBEC - Meads, Donald E. - Correspondence, "East-West Trade Proposal, Eaton", 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder 260)
  Correspondence re: with East European countries, replies to critical letters on trade development policy.
- IBEC - Purcell, Robert W., 1955-1968 (Box 26, Folder 261)
  Purcell served as chairman of Board, 1958-1968. Miscellaneous correspondence re: IBEC, reports to directors.
- IBEC - Rivet Co. Information, 1966-1967 (Box 26, Folder 262)
  Report on market trends of Rivets, January 5, 1967; notes on acquisition of J. L. Thompson Rivet and Machine Co.
- IBEC - Rodman C. Rockefeller, 1946-1971 (Box 26, Folder 263)
  Rodman C. Rockefeller elected President, June 12, 1968, press releases; management newsletters; miscellaneous agenda items; printed material; miscellaneous correspondence.
- IBEC - Double Ten Celebration, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 264)
- IBEC - Twentieth Anniversary Party, 1966-1968 (Box 26, Folder 265)
  Held in the Rainbow Room, NAR attended; audio tape; anniversary party guest list; transcript of NAR's remarks.
- IBEC - Stock, 1966-1971 (Box 26, Folder 266)
  Memos on stock options, common stock exchange, 1966 and miscellaneous correspondence re: IBEC economic activity.
- IBEC - Registration Statement, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 267)
  Form S-1 under Securities Act of 1933.
- AIA-IBEC - VBEC (Venezuelan Basic Economy Corporation) - NAR Trip to Venezuela, June 1947 (Box 27, Folder 268)
  Correspondence and memos re: NAR trip, December 1946-February 1947.
- AIA-IBEC - VBEC (Venezuelan Basic Economy Corporation) - President - R. Betancourt Correspondence, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 269)
- AIA-IBEC - VBEC (Venezuelan Basic Economy Corporation) - Report on Trip by NAR, June 14, 1947 - June 27, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 270)
  4 copies.
- AIA - General Correspondence and Memos, 1957-1965 (Box 27, Folder 271)
  Correspondence and memos re: studies, projects, programs, and proposals; reports re: "Cooperatives in Latin America," 1961; "An Interamerican Popular Information Program," 1957; correspondence re: phase-out of AIA programs 1967-1968.
- AIA - General Correspondence and Memos, 1965-1968 (Box 27, Folder 272)
- AIA - Reports - Information - Annual Reports, 1950, 1953-1957 (Box 27, Folder 273)
- AIA - Reports - Information - "The AIA Story by M. Dalrymple", 1968 (Box 27, Folder 274)
  Press release re: "The AIA Story by M. Dalrymple"; report on Information Program activities; memo re: AIA booklets; directory of U.S. Co.'s with operations in Latin America.
- AIA - Finances - Contributions, 1951-1969 (Box 28, Folder 275)
  Financial statements and reports; budgets; memos; progress reports; projects.
- AIA - Finances - Contributions - "Proposed Ten Year Program" 1960-1970, 1951-1965 (Box 28, Folder 276)
- AIA - Financial Statements, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 277)
- AIA - Treasurers Report Program Budget for 1967 (Box 28, Folder 278)
- AIA - Evaluation Survey, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 279)
  Appraisal of AIA Program; minutes of Exec. Committee meeting; memos re: evaluation survey; IRI (IBEC Research Institute) Advisory Board Meeting, May 27, 1963; Project agreement with Brazil.
- AIA - Michigan State University Agreement (Proposed), 1964-1965 (Box 28, Folder 280)
  Memos re: proposed agreement 1964.
- AIA - Reports and Information, 1962-1968 (Box 28, Folder 281)
- AIA - Reports - Progress, Condensed, 1960-1968 (Box 28, Folder 282)
  Condensed progress reports published at 3 month intervals 1965-1968; memos and comments; July-September 1960 report.
- AIA - Brazil - General, 1957-1960 (Box 29, Folder 283)
  Correspondence and memos re: ABCAR (Brazilian Association of Credit and Rural Assistance) and ACAR (Association of Credit and Rural Assistance) programs on Brazil, AIA, IRI (IBEC Research Institute); AIA Brazil budget.
- AIA - Brazil - ABCAR (Brazilian Association of Credit and Rural Assistance), 1958-1967 (Box 29, Folder 284)
  Correspondence and memos re: ABCAR (Brazilian Association of Credit and Rural Assistance) and Brazil.
- AIA - Brazil - ACAR (Association of Credit and Rural Assistance), 1958-1966, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 285)
  Correspondence and memos re: ACAR (Association of Credit and Rural Assistance); printed material on ACAR (Association of Credit and Rural Assistance). (Minas Gerais)
- AIA - Consejo de Bienestar Rural (CBR), 1952-1969 (Box 29, Folder 286)
  Correspondence and memos; copies of publication "Juventud Rural"; report on program development; report on CBR (Consejo de Bienestar Rural) and Venezuelan agriculture.
- AIA - Brazil - Costa Rica, 1958-1969 (Box 29, Folder 287)
  Correspondence and memos re: conservation project, population dynamics; printed material; miscellaneous memos and letters; reports of Programa Interamericano de Informacion Popular.
- AIA - Printed Material, 1963-1965 (Box 30, Folder 288)
  Publications and reports of AIA, PIJR (Programa Interamericano Para La Juventud Rural - Interamerican Rural Youth Program), etc.
- AIA - Margate, Fla. - House Plans, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 289)
  Floor plans for model homes.
- AIA - CBR (Consejo de Bienestar Rural) - Reports, 1954-1958 (Box 30, Folder 290)
  Reports on projects of CBR (Consejo de Bienestar Rural); proposed programs and budgets; Intermericana de Financiamento and Investimentos report to shareholders.
- AIA - CBR (Consejo de Bienestar Rural) - Reports, 1954, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 291)
- AIA - CBR (Consejo de Bienestar Rural) - Home Demonstration Agents School, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 292)
- AIA - Centro Comunal de Ciudad Ojeda, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 293)
- AIA - CIDEA (Inter-American Council on Nutrition Education) - Six Years Progress, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 294)
- AIA - Reports - Brazilian Economy, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 295)
- AIA - Reports - Education Photo Report #3, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 296)
  Cooperative Industrial Education Program Photographic Report, January 25, 1956.
- AIA - Reports - French Jones, 1951 (Box 31, Folder 297)
  Appraisal of the major AIA programs based on French and Jones survey, part one - Venezuela. May, 1951.
- AIA - Inter-American Rural Youth Program (PIJR), 1958, 1962-1971 (Box 31, Folder 298)
  Correspondence and memos re: 4-H support, work of AIA, miscellaneous correspondence; quarterly reports, newsletters; clippings publications, studies, reports.
- AIA - Minutes, Agendas, 1958-1961, 1965-1969 (Box 31, Folder 299)
  Minutes of annual and regular meetings of Board of Directors; notice of meetings; financial statements; agendas.
- IBEC - Agricultural Services (IAS), 1953-1968 (Box 32, Folder 300)
  Correspondence and memos re: IAS (IBEC Agricultural Services) projects, IBEC, IAS (IBEC Agricultural Services) budget and loans, IBEC Finance Committee; meetings.
- IBEC - Arbor Acres Farm, Inc., 1964-1971 (Box 32, Folder 301)
  Correspondence and memos re: cash requirements, poultry operations, etc., executive committee meetings; amendment to purchase Arbor Acres Farms, Inc., report - Arbor Acres Farms, Inc. Acquisition and Five Year Poultry Program, 1964.
- IBEC - CADA (Copmpania Anomina Distribuidora de Alimentos), 1949-1951, 1962, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 302)
  Correspondence and memos re: operations and sales of CADA (Copmpania Anomina Distribuidora de Alimentos) supermarkets, operations report December, 1951.
- IBEC - Cafes de Mexico, 1957-1970 (Box 32, Folder 303)
  Miscellaneous correspondence and memos re: Cafes de Mexico plant. Correspondents include NAR, Justo F. Fernandez.
- IBEC - Codival - Empreendimentos Crescinco - Brazil, 1956-1961 (Box 32, Folder 304)
  Crescinco; investment sheets, investment employment contract.
- IBEC - International Development Services, Inc. (IDS, Inc.), 1953-1964 (Box 32, Folder 305)
  Correspondence and memos re: IDS (International Development Services, Inc.) - AIA agreement, February 20, 1953; report on situations and prospects; appointments of directors, 1964.
- IBEC - Housing Corporation - General, 1955-1967 (Box 32, Folder 306)
  Memos re: stocks and stock holdings, real estate, finances, officers, meetings, agreements, etc., NAR resignation December 19, 1958.
- IBEC - IHC (International Housing Corporation) - Cinva Ram Block Press Branch, 1963-1967 (Box 32, Folder 307)
  Correspondence and memos re: availability and sales of Cinva Ram.
- IBEC - IHC (International Housing Corporation) - Middle East, 1953-1967 (Box 33, Folder 308)
  Memos re: contracts, budgets, agreements, finances, programs, and projects; telegrams re: exit visa.
- IBEC - IHC (International Housing Corporation) - President, [Taxes/Finance], 1955 (Box 33, Folder 309)
  Memos re: U.S. taxes, finance and financial statements. Correspondents include NAR, J. W. Hisle, L. Boyer.
- IBEC - IHC (International Housing Corporation) - President, [Argentina, Chile, Colombia, Peru], 1960-1963 (Box 33, Folder 310)
  Memos and correspondence re: housing in Argentina, Chile, Colombia, Peru. Correspondents include NAR, J. W. Hisle, L. Boyer.
- IBEC - IHC (International Housing Corporation) - Puerto Rico, 1949-1950, 1954-1967 (Box 33, Folder 311)
  Correspondence and memos re: reports, projects, resolutions, meetings, proposals, development layouts and land purchases; clippings; printed material; notes on Puerto Rican trip, August-November, 1965.
- IBEC - Economic Development Corporation, 1957-1969 (Box 33, Folder 312)
  Correspondence and memos re: operations, meetings; reports re: Bangkok, Thailand.
- IBEC - INCALA, Venezuela, 1954-1966 (Box 33, Folder 313)
  Correspondence and memos re: Venezuelan operations of INCALA, taxes, stock, milk option, prices, meetings and agreements.
- IBEC - Palmeras de Occidente, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 314)
  Memos re: finances, background de Palmeras, FINIBEC; chronology; Werner Report on the study of Palmeras de Occidente, S.A., March, 1967.
- IBEC - Research Institute - Technical Report on Corn, 1954 (Box 33, Folder 315)
- IBEC - Research Institute - Technical Report on Rice, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 316)
- IBEC - Research Institute - Progress Report - Brazil, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 317)
- IBEC - Informe Sobre el Programa Experimental de Arroz, Venezuela, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 318)
- IBEC - Research Institute - Progress Report, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 319)
- IBEC - Methods of Measuring Pasture Production Lectures, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 320)
- IBEC - Results of Stilbestrol in Fattening Grass Fed Zebu Cattle in Brazil, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 321)
- IBEC - Research Institute - Progress Report, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 322)
- IBEC - Research Institute - Progress Report, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 323)
- IBEC - Research Institute - General Correspondence, 1951, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 324)
  Request for information on research results; letter re: meeting of institute.
- IBEC - Research Institute - AIA, 1948-1970 (Box 35, Folder 325)
  NAR comments on first annual report. Office space. Insurance policy on NAR's life. Personnel changes.
- IBEC - Stock, 1956-1967 (Box 35, Folder 326)
  Sale of stock to employees. Changes in stock structure.
- IBEC - Research Institute - IRI (IBEC Research Institute) - General, 1963-1971 (Box 35, Folder 327)
  Correspondence and memos from proposals for a research foundation to IRI (IBEC Research Institute) and AIA merger; clippings, articles; reports; memos re: meetings, proposals, budgets, programs, operations status, projects, etc.
- IBEC - Research Institute - IRI (IBEC Research Institute) - General, 1959-1963 (Box 35, Folder 328)
- IBEC - Research Institute - IRI (IBEC Research Institute) - General, 1957-1959 (Box 35, Folder 329)
- IBEC - Research Institute - IRI (IBEC Research Institute) - General, 1957-1958 (Box 35, Folder 330)
- IBEC - Research Institute - IRI (IBEC Research Institute) - General, 1955-1957 (Box 35, Folder 331)
- IBEC - Research Institute - IRI (IBEC Research Institute) - General, 1953-1954 (Box 35, Folder 332)
- IBEC - Research Institute - IRI (IBEC Research Institute) - General, 1950-1952 (Box 36, Folder 333)
- IBEC - Research Institute - IRI (IBEC Research Institute) - Corn Program, 1953 (Box 36, Folder 334)
  Memos and progress reports re: Venezuelan corn programs.
- IBEC - Research Institute - IRI (IBEC Research Institute) - Ecuador, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 335)
  Copy of "Program to Improve Economic Development of Ecuador" by Dr. Ferdinand P. Mehrlich.
- IBEC - Research Institute - IRI (IBEC Research Institute) - Rice Programs, 1953 (Box 36, Folder 336)
  Progress reports for Venezuelan rice programs.
- IBEC - Research Institute - IRI (IBEC Research Institute) - Finances, 1952-1962 (Box 36, Folder 337)
  Financial statements; budget letters; correspondence and memos re: programs, statements, budgets, finances; reports - 1955 proposed program and budget for IRI (IBEC Research Institute) - Brazil.
- IBEC - Supermarkets - General Correspondence, 1955-1968 (Box 36, Folder 338)
  Correspondence and memos re: supermarkets in Venezuela, CADA (Compania Anomina Distribuidora de Alimentos), Puerto Rico, mobile stores, etc., financial statement.
- IBEC - Supermarkets - Argentina, 1960-1965 (Box 36, Folder 339)
  Correspondence re: land, initial operations. Correspondents include NAR, Richard W. Boogaart.
- IBEC - Supermarkets - Boogaart, R. W., 1956-1968 (Box 37, Folder 340)
  Correspondence re: Boogaart's survey of European countries for supermarket projects, Italy, Dasca stock and Argentina.
- IBEC - Supermarkets - Europe, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 341)
  Correspondence re: Boogaart's trip through Europe to survey supermarket conditions; Boogaart's report on supermarket possibilities.
- IBEC - Supermarkets - Italy, 1956-1962 (Box 37, Folder 342)
  Correspondence re: establishment and operations of supermarkets; initiation of food retailing project in Italy; enlargement of original operation. Correspondents include R. W. Boogaart, W. D. Bradford.
- IBEC - Thailand Ltd. - Design Thai, 1965-1969 (Box 37, Folder 343)
  Correspondence and memos re: Design Thai, history of IBEC in Thailand, budget for Design Thai, invitation list for Design Thai Fashion Show, March 3, 1966.
- IBEC - Trainee Program - Termination of Employment, 1949-1962 (Box 37, Folder 344)
  Memos and letters re: acceptance into trainee program and termination of programs, termination of employment.
- IBEC - VBEC (Venezuelan Basic Economy Corporation) - Venezuela, 1954, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 345)
  Memos re: status of VBEC (Venezuelan Basic Economy Corporation); merger of VBEC (Venezuelan Basic Economy Corporation) and IBEC, December 31, 1954; projects; meeting notes.
- IBEC - VBEC (Venezuelan Basic Economy Corporation) - Foot Mouth Disease, May - September 1947 (Box 37, Folder 346)
  Correspondence re: hoof and mouth disease among cattle in Venezuela. Correspondents include Mr. Kempton.
- IBEC - Investing Corporation Bank - Certificate of Incorporation, By-Laws, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 347)
- IBEC - Investing Corporation Bank, 1949-1966 (Box 37, Folder 348)
  Correspondence re: bank and checking accounts of IIC, statements; bank statements, checkbooks, bankbook.
- IBEC - Investing Corporation - Correspondence, 1948-1966 (Box 38, Folder 349)
  Correspondence and memos re: corporation, officers, meetings, stocks, finances.
- IBEC - Investing Corporation - Federal Corporation Income Taxes, 1948-1966 (Box 38, Folder 350)